PrivyGate is a privacy-preserving multi-authority attribute authorization prototype for autonomous agents on 0G.
It is built for cases where an agent needs access to private data or protected tools,
but the user should not reveal their full identity or every credential they own.
Wallet ownership is not enough for real access control. PrivyGate turns access into a policy proof instead of identity disclosure.
Independent authorities issue attributes, such as university status or lab role.
The requester creates an authorization signature for a specific tool call and policy.
0G Chain acts as the auditable registry, and 0G Storage stores the redacted audit manifest.
Here Alice has both required attributes: University role student and Lab role researcher.
Her agent requests access to private-dataset.read. PrivyGate verifies that the policy is satisfied and returns accept.
Now Bob tries the same request. Bob only has the university student attribute.
He does not have the lab researcher credential, so the policy cannot be satisfied and the request is rejected.
Next, Alice's lab researcher credential is revoked.
After revocation, her old authorization no longer verifies.
This contract is the 0G registry layer. It records authorities, policy hashes, revocation state, and verification events.
The storage audit manifest stores redacted policy metadata, decision hashes, and public chain evidence.
This hackathon version uses a symbolic field backend. It validates the workflow, but it is not production cryptography yet.
PrivyGate demonstrates multi-authority, revocable, policy-based private authorization with Chain and Storage evidence on 0G.